Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society institutional records ARC.288
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 8: Exhibitions and Special Projects, circa 1865-2020
  - Sub-series 8.5: Brooklyn Works: 400 Years of Making a Living in Brooklyn, 1988-2007, bulk 1996-2003
    - Period 1 and 2 -- Slavery Research, circa 2001 (Box 299, Folder 1-2)
    - Period 2 -- African American Stories -- Bibliog Cards, circa 1996-2003 (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Period 2 -- African American Stories -- Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Period 2 -- Atlantic Docks and Other 1840s Labor Struggles, circa 1996-2003 (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Period 2 -- Atlantic Docks, Archival Materials List, circa 2000-2003 (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - Period 2 -- Atlantic Docks, Background Info, circa 1996-2003 (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - Period 2 -- Atlantic Docks, Images, circa 1996-2002 (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Period 2 -- Atlantic Docks, Narratives, circa 2000-2003 (Box 299, Folder 9)
    - Period 2 -- Beginning of Manufacturing, circa 1996-2002 (Box 299, Folder 10)
    - Period 2 -- Brooklyn Village, circa 1996-2003 (Box 299, Folder 11)
    - Period 2 -- Civil War Abolitionists, circa 2002 (Box 299, Folder 12)
    - Period 2 -- Draft Riot Research, 2001 (Box 299, Folder 13)
    - Period 2 -- Empire Stores Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 299, Folder 14)
    - Period 2 -- Exhibit Script [draft], circa 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Period 2 -- Expanding Brooklyn, Background Info, circa 1996-2003 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Period 2 -- Expanding Brooklyn, Historical Overview, circa 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Period 2 -- Expanding Brooklyn, Maps List, circa 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Period 2 -- Expanding Brooklyn, Narratives, circa 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Period 2 -- Ferry Pilots Strike, circa 2002 (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Period 2 -- Introductory Panel, circa 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Period 2 -- Irish Population (1860-1900), 2002 (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - Period 2 -- Joshua Sands Narrative, circa 2000-2002 (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Period 2 -- Manufacturing Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Period 2 -- Margaret Brown Room, circa 1996-2003 (Box 300, Folder 11)
    - Period 2 -- Maritcha Lyons Research, circa 1998 (Box 300, Folder 12)
    - Period 2 -- Mercantile and Manufacturing Town [Script], circa 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 13)
    - Period 2 -- Mile-Marker Info, circa 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 14)
    - Period 2 -- Objects and Images, 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 15-16)
    - Period 2 -- Pratt's Oil Works Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 300, Folder 17)
    - Period 2 -- Product Barrels, circa 1996-2003 (Box 300, Folder 18)
    - Period 2 -- Racial Discrimination, circa 2000-2003 (Box 300, Folder 19)
    - Period 2 -- Race Relations, circa 1996-2002 (Box 300, Folder 20)
    - Period 2 -- Rejected Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 300, Folder 21)
    - Period 2 -- Ropewalk, Background, circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Period 2 -- Ropewalk, Chatham England Rope, circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Period 2 -- Ropewalk, Historical Perspectives [Slides], circa 2000 (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Period 2 -- Ropewalk, Images, circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Period 2 -- [Ropewalk, Literary Resource Summary], circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Period 2 -- Ropewalk, Narrative Possibilities, circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Period 2 -- Ropewalk, Objects, circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Period 2 -- Ropewalk, Personal Narratives, circa 2000-2002 (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Period 2 -- Ropewalk, Research, 1996-2003 (Box 301, Folder 9-10)
    - Period 2 -- Warehouse, Archival Documents List, circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 11)
    - Period 2 -- Warehouse, Historical Overview, circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 12)
    - Period 2 -- Warehouse, Images, circa 2000-2003 (Box 301, Folder 13)
    - Period 2 -- Warehouse, Laws, circa 1996-2003 (Box 301, Folder 14)
    - Period 2 -- Warehouse, Maps List, circa 2000-2003 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Period 2 -- Warehouse, Narratives, circa 2000-2003 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Period 2 -- Warehouse, Objects, circa 2000-2003 (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - Period 2 -- Warehouse, Research, circa 1996-2002 (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - Period 2 -- Waterfront, Docks Research, circa 1996-2002 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - Period 2 -- Waterfront, Images, circa 2000-2003 (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - Period 2 -- Waterfront, Narrative Possibilities, circa 2000-2003 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - Period 2 -- Waterfront, Pierrepont Stores, circa 2000 (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - Period 2 -- Willis Hodges Narrative, circa 2000-2002 (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - Period 2 and 3 -- DUMBO Research, circa 2000 (Box 302, Folder 10)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Boots and Shoes, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 11)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Flax, Hemp, and Jute, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 12)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Food Production, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 13)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Glass, Brick, Tile, Pottery, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 14)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Industrial Directory Research, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 15)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, List of Industries in Brooklyn, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 16)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Metal Works and Machinery, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 17)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Oils and Miscellaneous, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 18)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Printing and Bookbinding, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 19)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Industries, Tailoring, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 20)
    - Period 3 -- 1913 Map of Industrial Firms in Brooklyn, 2001-2003 (Box 302, Folder 21)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Biographies, 2001-2002 (Box 302, Folder 22)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Candidates, 2002 (Box 302, Folder 23)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Chair, 2000-2001 (Box 302, Folder 24)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Historical Overview, circa 2000-2003 (Box 302, Folder 25)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Images, 2002 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Interview Notes, 2002 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Oral Histories, 1999-2001 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Personal Narratives, circa 2000-2003 (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Pole, 2002 (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Research, 2002-2003 (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - Period 3 -- Barbershop Script, 2002 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - Period 3 -- Black Stories, Barbershop, circa 1996-2002 (Box 303, Folder 8)
    - Period 3 -- Brooklyn Brewery Visit, 2000 June (Box 303, Folder 9)
    - Period 3 -- Bush Terminal, Background Info, circa 2000 (Box 303, Folder 10)
    - Period 3 -- Bush Terminal, Historical Overview, circa 1999-2003 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Period 3 -- Bush Terminal, Images, 1998-2001 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - Period 3 -- Bush Terminal, Personal Narratives, circa 1999-2003 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Period 3 -- Clipboard Interactive, Oil and Sugar Routes, circa 1996-2003 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Period 3 -- Computer Interactive [Images], 2002 (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Period 3 -- [Conceptual Plan], 2001 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Period 3 -- Docks and Longshoremen Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Period 3 -- Docks, Background Info, 1999-2001 (Box 304, Folder 8)
    - Period 3 -- Docks, Historical Overview, circa 1999-2003 (Box 304, Folder 9)
    - Period 3 -- Docks, Images [Rejected], circa 1999-2003 (Box 304, Folder 10)
    - Period 3 -- Docks, Narratives, circa 1999-2003 (Box 304, Folder 11)
    - Period 3 -- Docks, Objects, circa 1999-2003 (Box 304, Folder 12)
    - Period 3 -- Drake's Cakes Research, 2000-2002 (Box 304, Folder 13)
    - Period 3 -- Ebinger, 2002 (Box 304, Folder 14)
    - Period 3 -- Ebony Ads, 2002 (Box 304, Folder 15)
    - Period 3 -- Emmanuel House, circa 1999-2003 (Box 304, Folder 16)
    - Period 3 -- Exhibit Script [draft], circa 2000-2003 (Box 304, Folder 17)
    - Period 3 -- Garment Factory, Background Info, circa 1996-2002 (Box 304, Folder 18)
    - Period 3 -- Garment Factory, Historical Overview, circa 2001 (Box 304, Folder 19)
    - Period 3 -- Garment Factory, Images, 2001 (Box 304, Folder 20)
    - Period 3 -- Garment Factory, Objects, 1996 (Box 304, Folder 21)
    - Period 3 -- Garment Factory, Personal Narratives, circa 1999-2002 (Box 304, Folder 22)
    - Period 3 -- General Background Info, circa 1996-2003 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - Period 3 -- Image Possibilities, circa 1996-2003 (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - Period 3 -- Intro Panel [draft], circa 2000-2003 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Period 3 -- Irving Bush, 2001 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Period 3 -- Industry and Manufacturing Images, circa 1999-2003 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Period 3 -- Introduction, Historical Overview, circa 1999-2003 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Period 3 -- Introduction, Narratives, circa 1999-2003 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Period 3 -- Key Objects, circa 2000-2003 (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - Period 3 -- Local and Community Images, circa 1999-2003 (Box 305, Folder 9)
    - Period 3 -- Longshoremen Strikes, circa 1996-2002 (Box 305, Folder 10)
    - Period 3 -- Magliano Family, circa 1996-2003 (Box 305, Folder 11)
    - Period 3 -- Maps, circa 1999-2003 (Box 305, Folder 12)
    - Period 3 -- Middle-Sized Industries, Eberhard Faber, circa 1999-2002 (Box 305, Folder 13)
    - Period 3 -- Middle-Sized Industries, Pfizer Images, circa 1999-2002 (Box 305, Folder 14)
    - Period 3 -- Middle-Sized Industries, Squibb Images, circa 1999-2002 (Box 305, Folder 15)
    - Period 3 -- Newsies, Background Info, 1998-2001 (Box 305, Folder 16)
    - Period 3 -- Newsies, Historical Overview, circa 2001 (Box 305, Folder 17)
    - Period 3 -- Newsies, Images, 2000-2001 (Box 305, Folder 18)
    - Period 3 -- Newsies, Objects, circa 1999-2002 (Box 305, Folder 19)
    - Period 3 -- Newsies, Personal Narratives, circa 1999-2002 (Box 305, Folder 20)
    - Period 3 -- Newspaper Printing Industry, circa 1996-2003 (Box 305, Folder 21)
    - Period 3 -- Objects and Images, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 1-3)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Barbershop, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Biography of a Chinaman, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Black Longshoremen, circa 1996-2003 (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Chicago Stockyards, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Chicago Teamster, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 8)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Collar Starcher, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 9)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Freddie Pratt, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Geelan Photos, 2000 (Box 306, Folder 11)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, General Longshoremen, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 12)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Hackman, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 13)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Irish Cook, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 14)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Irish Immigrants, 2000-2002 (Box 306, Folder 15)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, "New Slavery in the South", circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 16)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Nurse, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 17)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Pushcart Peddler, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 18)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Salesgirl, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 19)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Streetcar Conductor, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 20)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Sweatshop Girl, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 21)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, A Tramp's Tale, circa 2000-2003 (Box 306, Folder 22)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Washerwoman, circa 1996-2003 (Box 306, Folder 23)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Widow's Autobiography, circa 1996-2003 (Box 306, Folder 24)
    - Period 3 -- Personal Narratives, Workers Speak Table of Contents, circa 1996-2003 (Box 306, Folder 25)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall Company Research, 2002-2003 (Box 307, Folder 1-2)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, A and P, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Barbicide, 2001 (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Barnes, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Barton's, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Bazooka Gum, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Beech-Nut Coffee, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Benjamin Moore, 2002 (Box 308, Folder 7)
      Contains 1 disk.
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Bliss Co., circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Bohack, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 9)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Brillo, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 10)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Bush Terminal, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 11)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Chiclets, 2003 (Box 308, Folder 12)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Chock Full O'Nuts, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 13)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Cricket Records, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 14)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Dairy Companies, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 15)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Devoe, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 16)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Drake's Cakes, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 17)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Dunlap Hats, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 18)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Eberhard Faber, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 19)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Eiker's, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 20)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Entenmann's, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 21)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, E.R. Squibb, 2003 (Box 308, Folder 22)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Ex-Lax, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 23)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Grand Union, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 24)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Higgins, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 25)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Kentile, 2001 (Box 308, Folder 26)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Kirkman, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 27)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Knox Hats, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 28)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Lily Cups, 2002 (Box 308, Folder 29)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, McLoughlin, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 30)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Mergenthaler, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 31)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Oakite, 2001 (Box 308, Folder 32)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Other Breweries, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 33)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Pfizer, 2001 (Box 308, Folder 34)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Piels, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 35)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Polly-O, 2001 (Box 308, Folder 36)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Revlon, 2001 (Box 308, Folder 37)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Rheingold, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 38)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Royal Baking, 2001 (Box 308, Folder 39)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Sandford, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 40)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Schaefer, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 41)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Sperry Gyroscope, 2001 (Box 308, Folder 42)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, St. Joseph's, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 43)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Topps, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 44)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Trommer, circa 2000-2003 (Box 308, Folder 45)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Uneeda, 2000 (Box 308, Folder 46)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Virginia Dare, 2002-2003 (Box 308, Folder 47)
    - Period 3 -- Product Wall, Warshaw, 2002 (Box 308, Folder 48)
    - Period 3 -- Rejected Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Period 3 -- Retail and Service Images, circa 1999-2003 (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Period 3 -- Sone and Fleming Oil Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Archival Documents List, circa 2001 (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Background Info, 1999-2001 (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Domino Sugar Literary Resources, 1996-1999 (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Domino Sugar Objects, 1999-2003 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Domino Sugar Timeline, 2003 (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Domino Sugar Today, 2000-2003 (Box 309, Folder 9)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Domino Sugar Visit, 1994-1999 (Box 309, Folder 10)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, "How Sugar Was Made", 2003 (Box 309, Folder 11)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Images, 2002 (Box 310, Folder 1-2)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Newspaper Articles, 1999-2001 (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Personal Narratives, 2001-2002 (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Period 3 -- Sugar, Sugar Workers, 1999 (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Period 3 -- Sweatshops, circa 1999-2003 (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Period 3 -- Tenement, Historical Overview, circa 1999-2002 (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - Period 3 -- Tenement, Images, circa 1999-2003 (Box 310, Folder 8)
    - Period 3 -- Tenement, Objects, circa 1999-2002 (Box 310, Folder 9)
    - Period 3 -- Tenement, Personal Narratives, circa 1999-2003 (Box 310, Folder 10)
    - Period 3 -- Time Clock, 2000 (Box 310, Folder 11)
    - Period 3 -- Timeline, circa 1999-2002 (Box 310, Folder 12)
    - Period 3 -- Trolley Images, 2000 (Box 310, Folder 13)
    - Period 3 -- Trolley Strike, 2000-2001 (Box 310, Folder 14)
    - Period 3 -- Waterfront, Docks, Warehouses, Transportation, circa 1990s (Box 310, Folder 15)
    - Period 3 -- Waterfront, Images, circa 1999-2002 (Box 310, Folder 16)
    - Period 3 -- W.E.B DuBois, circa 1996-2003 (Box 310, Folder 17)
    - Period 3 -- "When Worker's Speak, Translating the Past in Brooklyn" [article], 2003 (Box 310, Folder 18)
    - Period 3 -- Women and Work, 1994-2002 (Box 310, Folder 19)
    - Period 3 and 4 -- Exhibit Concept Layout, 2001 (Box 505, Folder 2)
    - Period 3 and 4 -- Exhibit Development, 2000-2001 (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Period 3 and 4 -- Personal Narratives, Transit Worker, circa 1996-2003 (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Period 4 -- Asian Immigration and Jobs, 1993-1997 (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Period 4 -- Background, Containerization and Demographics, 1998-2001 (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Period 4 -- Bed-Stuy, 1996 (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Period 4 -- Beth-El Hospital Strike, 1999 (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Period 4 -- Brooklyn Artisans, 1998 (Box 311, Folder 7)
    - Period 4 -- Brooklyn Economic Development Corporation Conference, 2000-2001 (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - Period 4 -- Brooklyn Navy Yard, Clippings, 1994-2003 (Box 311, Folder 9)
    - Period 4 -- Brooklyn Navy Yard, Images, 2002 (Box 311, Folder 10)
    - Period 4 -- Brooklyn Navy Yard, New Navy Yard, 1997-2001 (Box 311, Folder 11)
    - Period 4 -- Brooklyn Navy Yard, Research, 1994-1997 (Box 311, Folder 12)
    - Period 4 -- Brooklyn Navy Yard, Visit, 1996 (Box 311, Folder 13)
    - Period 4 -- Bushwick Worker's Rally, 2001 January (Box 311, Folder 14)
    - Period 4 -- Bushwick Worker's Rights, 1999-2001 (Box 311, Folder 15)
    - Period 4 -- Census 2000, Newest New Yorkers, 1995-2000 (Box 311, Folder 16)
    - Period 4 -- Census 2000, Segregation, 2001 (Box 311, Folder 17)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Apparel/Sweatshops, 1998-2001 (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Brooklyn Jobs, 1996-1997 (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Brooklyn Manufacturing Directory, 1998 (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Economic Struggling, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Economy Images, 1996-2001 (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Interviews, 2001-2002 (Box 312, Folder 6-7)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Labor Images, 2002 (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Labor Struggles, 1994-2000 (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Manufacturing and Immigration, 1997-2000 (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Manufacturing and Industrialization, 1994-1996 (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Non-Manufacturing, 1997-1999 (Box 312, Folder 12)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Sugar Workers, circa 2000-2003 (Box 312, Folder 13)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Tech Work in Brooklyn, 2000 (Box 312, Folder 14)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Waterfront Images, circa 1999-2003 (Box 312, Folder 15)
    - Period 4 -- Contemporary Work Images, circa 1996-2003 (Box 312, Folder 16)
    - Period 4 -- Current Industry, 1988-1996 (Box 312, Folder 17-18)
    - Period 4 -- De-industrial Transition, Background Info, 1999-2001 (Box 312, Folder 19)
    - Period 4 -- De-industrial Transition, Images, circa 1996-2002 (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Period 4 -- De-industrial Transition, Objects, circa 1996-2002 (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - Period 4 -- Demise of Manufacturing and Shipping, 1996-2000 (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Period 4 -- Downsizing Articles, 1996 (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - Period 4 -- Eiker Object Images, 2000 (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Period 4 -- Exhibit Script (with Images), 2002 (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Period 4 -- Garment Sweatshops Today, 1999 (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Period 4 -- General Background Info, 2000-2001 (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - Period 4 -- General Immigration and the New Economy, 1996-1999 (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Period 4 -- General Work Issues, 2000-2001 (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - Period 4 -- Hertzling Bros, 1988 (Box 313, Folder 11)
    - Period 4 -- High Tech Brooklyn, 1996-2001 (Box 313, Folder 12)
    - Period 4 -- Historical Overview, circa 2002 (Box 313, Folder 13)
    - Period 4 -- Immigration and Jobs, 1996 (Box 313, Folder 14)
    - Period 4 -- Inequality of Wealth, 1995-1999 (Box 313, Folder 15)
    - Period 4 -- Interpretive Concept, 2001 (Box 313, Folder 16)
    - Period 4 -- Joblessness, 1997-2001 (Box 313, Folder 17)
    - Period 4 -- Latino Job Issues, 2001 (Box 313, Folder 18)
    - Period 4 -- Lockers, Archival Materials List, circa 1999-2002 (Box 313, Folder 19)
    - Period 4 -- Lockers, Drake's, circa 2001-2002 (Box 313, Folder 20)
    - Period 4 -- Lockers, Hospital Workers Research and Notes, 2002 (Box 313, Folder 21-22)
    - Period 4 -- Lockers, Objects, circa 1999-2002 (Box 313, Folder 23)
    - Period 4 -- Low Wage and Service Work, 1995-2000 (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Period 4 -- Miscellaneous Prints, circa 1996-2003 (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Period 4 -- Multilingual Strike Broadsides, 2000-2002 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Period 4 -- Neighborhood Guides, circa 1996-2003 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Period 4 -- New Immigrant Images, circa 1999-2003 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Period 4 -- New York Metro Region Economy, 1996-2000 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Period 4 -- Newspaper Clippings, 1996-2001 (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Period 4 -- Panel Label Text, circa 2001-2002 (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - Period 4 -- Personal Narratives, Chinese Immigrants, 1993-1994 (Box 314, Folder 9)
    - Period 4 -- Personal Narratives, Containerization and Longshore Work Today, circa 1996-2003 (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - Period 4 -- Personal Narratives, Soviet Immigrants, circa 2000 (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - Period 4 -- Personal Narratives, Unemployed, 1996 (Box 314, Folder 12)
    - Period 4 -- Personal Narratives, Women Telephone Workers, circa 1996-2003 (Box 314, Folder 13)
    - Period 4 -- Puerto Rican Images, circa 2000-2003 (Box 314, Folder 14)
    - Period 4 -- Race Relations, circa 1997 (Box 314, Folder 15)
    - Period 4 -- Rotunda Orientation, circa 2000 (Box 314, Folder 16)
    - Period 4 -- Russian/Eastern Europeans, Immigration and Jobs, 1998-2001 (Box 314, Folder 17)